

Siddharth Mishra

Python Developer

Analytical and motivated professional developer offering 3+ years of experience designing and debugging Python applications/scripts. Hoping to advance my development skills to meet increasing customer requirements and add value to the company.

mishra07.siddharth@gmail.com 9302323026 Pengaluru, India

https://github.com/siddharth07-ui https://www.linkedin.com/in/siddmi/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python Django AWS CI/CD Flask Git SQL MongoDB JQuery JavaScript

CSS HTML Redis OOPs

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Developer

Gnani.ai

09/2022 - 09/2023 Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Developed and maintained 15+ production Python conversational AI applications
- Used Numpy and Pandas to perform data analysis and visualization
- Optimized Python code to reduce execution time by 50%
- Designed and developed a Flask API that served over 50,000 requests per day

Azure Cloud Engineer Mindtree LTD

02/2020 - 06/2022 Hyderabad, Telangana

- Worked in conjunction with the data migration team to perform clean and precise data migration plans.
- Responsibility for situations where need to investigate suspicious behavior in assets/storage devices.
- o Also, experience in automating daily and repetitive tasks using Python scripting.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) -- Computer Science

Chhattisgarh Swami Vivekanand Technical University

06/2014 - 06/2018 Computer Science

o Developed an application using Android Studio for parent- teacher meeting

CERTIFICATIONS

Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer ---- Udemy

INTERESTS

Reading Novels